[{
    "question": "Who wrote an incomplete 2 movement symphonic work commonly called the 'Unfinished' Symphony?",
    "choice1": "Schubert",
    "choice2": "Mozart",
    "choice3": "Bach",
    "choice4": "Berlioz",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "'For Unto Us a Child Is Born', 'The Trumpet Shall Sound', and 'Hallelujah' are sections of what oratorio?",
    "choice1": "St Matthew Passion",
    "choice2": "Solomon",
    "choice3": "Israel in Egypt",
    "choice4": "Messiah",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of these composers is NOT one of the noted '3 B's'?",
    "choice1": "Bartok",
    "choice2": "Brahms",
    "choice3": "Beethoven",
    "choice4": "Bach",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {  
    "question": "The majority of works by Frédéric Chopin were written for what instrument?",
    "choice1": "Clarinet",
    "choice2": "Flute",
    "choice3": "Piano",
    "choice4": "Violin",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of these percussion instruments is tunable to different pitches?",
    "choice1": "Snare Drum",
    "choice2": "Timpani",
    "choice3": "Tam Tam",
    "choice4": "Bass Drum",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "In a symphony orchestra, who is the 'concertmaster'?",
    "choice1": "Pincipal oboist",
    "choice2": "Conductor",
    "choice3": "Orchestral manager",
    "choice4": "First chair first violinist",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "What musical ensemble would perform pieces scored for 'SATB'?",
    "choice1": "Concert Band",
    "choice2": "Chorus",
    "choice3": "String Quartet",
    "choice4": "Orchestra",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "At the start of an orchestral performance, to what pitch does the orchestra tune?",
    "choice1": "Middle C",
    "choice2": "Concert A",
    "choice3": "Concert F",
    "choice4": "Concert B flat",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of these instruments is NOT a double reed instrument?",
    "choice1": "Oboe",
    "choice2": "Cor Anglais",
    "choice3": "Bassoon",
    "choice4": "Clarinet",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which of these choices has musical eras in the correct order, from earliest to most modern?",
    "choice1": "Baroque, Renaissance, Romantic, Classical",
    "choice2": "Classical, Renaissance, Romantic, Baroque",
    "choice3": "Renaissance, Baroque, Classical, Romantic",
    "choice4": "Renaissance, Classical, Baroque, Romantic",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "In Prokofiev's Peter and the Wolf, the duck is portrayed by what instrument?",
    "choice1": "Oboe",
    "choice2": "Muted Trumpet",
    "choice3": "Clarinet",
    "choice4": "Cello",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which one of these operas was composed by Rossini?",
    "choice1": "Aida",
    "choice2": "The Marriage of Figaro",
    "choice3": "The Barber of Seville",
    "choice4": "Fidelio",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "The musical form of fugue is associated most often with what musical era?",
    "choice1": "Baroque",
    "choice2": "Classical",
    "choice3": "Romantic",
    "choice4": "Modern",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "Which one of these is a Romantic Era composer?",
    "choice1": "George Frideric Handel",
    "choice2": "Gustav Mahler",
    "choice3": "Aaron Copland",
    "choice4": "Joseph Haydn",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "The sackbut was the predecessor of what modern musical instrument?",
    "choice1": "French Horn",
    "choice2": "Bassoon",
    "choice3": "Viola",
    "choice4": "Trombone",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "In classical era sonata form, the second theme of the exposition is traditionally presented in what key?",
    "choice1": "Tonic",
    "choice2": "Subdominant",
    "choice3": "Dominant",
    "choice4": "Minor",
    "answer": "3"
  }, {   
    "question": "Who wrote the March 'Liberty Bell'? ",
    "choice1": "George Gershwin",
    "choice2": "John Philip Sousa",
    "choice3": "Edward Elgar",
    "choice4": "Gustav Holst",
    "answer": "2"
  }, {   
    "question": "In what century did Tchaikovsky live?",
    "choice1": "19th",
    "choice2": "18th",
    "choice3": "20th",
    "choice4": "17th",
    "answer": "1"
  }, {   
    "question": "Who composed the 'Funeral March'?",
    "choice1": "Claude Debussy",
    "choice2": "Alban Berg",
    "choice3": "Edward Grieg",
    "choice4": "Frederic Chopin",
    "answer": "4"
  }, {   
    "question": "How many strings does a Harp have",
    "choice1": "206",
    "choice2": "46",
    "choice3": "106",
    "choice4": "16",
  "answer": "2" } ]